[
  {
    "question": "Where does Rory attend college?",
    "choices": ["Harvard", "Yale", "Princeton", "Stanford"],
    "answer": "Yale"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who owns Luke's Diner?",
    "choices": ["Kirk", "Luke", "Taylor", "Sookie"],
    "answer": "Luke"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Lorelai's dog?",
    "choices": ["Paul Anka", "Cinnamon", "Brian", "Bob"],
    "answer": "Paul Anka"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Rory's best friend?",
    "choices": ["Paris", "Lane", "Madeline", "April"],
    "answer": "Lane"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the town where the show is set?",
    "choices": ["Stars Hollow", "Riverdale", "Sunnydale", "Mystic Falls"],
    "answer": "Stars Hollow"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Rory's first boyfriend?",
    "choices": ["Jess", "Dean", "Logan", "Tristan"],
    "answer": "Dean"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Lorelai's mother?",
    "choices": ["Emily", "Sookie", "Babette", "Trix"],
    "answer": "Emily"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the inn that Lorelai and Sookie work at?",
    "choices": ["The Dragonfly Inn", "The Gilded Lily", "The Rosewood Inn", "The Blue Moon Inn"],
    "answer": "The Dragonfly Inn"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Rory's younger brother?",
    "choices": ["Logan", "Jess", "Dean", "None"],
    "answer": "None"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the actor who plays Luke?",
    "choices": ["Scott Patterson", "Matt Czuchry", "Jared Padalecki", "Keiko Agena"],
    "answer": "Scott Patterson"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the actor who plays Lorelai?",
    "choices": ["Lauren Graham", "Alexis Bledel", "Kelly Bishop", "Melissa McCarthy"],
    "answer": "Lauren Graham"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the actor who plays Rory?",
    "choices": ["Alexis Bledel", "Lauren Graham", "Kelly Bishop", "Melissa McCarthy"],
    "answer": "Alexis Bledel"
  },
  {
    "question":"Where did Sookie work with Joe?", 
    "choices": ["Deerfield Lodge", "Oak Tree Bed & Breakfast", "Pacos Tacos", "The Gilded Lily"],
    "answer": "Deerfield Lodge"
  },
  {
    "question":"Who is the headmaster at Chilton?",
    "choices": ["Charleston", "Medina", "Michele", "Fleming"],
    "answer": "Charleston"
  },
  {
    "question":"What did Lorelai name the fish she caught when she went fishing with Alex?", 
    "choices": ["Lane", "Anna", "Shirley", "Jane"],
    "answer": "Jane"
  },
    {
    "question":"What book did Jess 'borrow' from Rory?", 
    "choices": ["Howl", "Oliver Twist", "Swan's Way", "Anna Karenina"],
    "answer": "Howl"
  },
  {
    "question": "What number does Rory have on her back for the Dance Marathon?",
    "choices": ["78", "76", "67", "17"],
    "answer": "67"
  },
  {
    "question" :"What flowers does Max Medina have delivered to The Dragonfly Inn?",
    "choices": ["Roses", "Carnations", "Lilies", "Daisies"],
    "answer": "Daisies"
  },
    {
    "question" :"What is the name of the Novel Jess wrote?",
    "choices": ["The Separation", "The Subject", "The Subsect", "The Tea"],
    "answer": "The Subsect"
  },
    {
    "question" :"What is the name of the publisher Jess works for?",
    "choices": ["Trental Books", "Scholastic Books", "Trench Books", "Truncheon Books"],
    "answer": "Truncheon Books"
  },
  {
    "question" :"How many pairs of Jimmy Choos did Lorelai figure out she could buy with the money from her dad?",
    "choices": ["100", "125", "150", "170"],
    "answer": "150"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the secret society Logan is in?",
    "choices": ["The Life and Death Brigade", "The Life and Death Idea", "The Puffs", "The Trust Fund Kids"],
    "answer": "The Life and Death Brigade"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the license plate number on Lorelai's Jeep?",
    "choices": ["937-G5R","956-G4P","397-G9Q","793-R5G"],
    "answer": "937-G5R"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was Luke's dad's Hardware Store called?",
    "choices": ["Williams Hardware","Danes Hardware","W. Danes Hardware","Danes Odds and Ends"],
    "answer": "Williams Hardware"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does Richard Gilmore eat for breakfast everyday?",
    "choices": ["Half a Grapefruit","Half a Orange","Oatmeal","Toast"],
    "answer": "Half a Grapefruit"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many community service hours does Rory get?",
    "choices": ["600","500","300","200"],
    "answer": "300"
  },
  {
    "question": "During which class did Lorelai break her leg?",
    "choices": ["Yoga","Pilates","Zumba","Pole Dancing"],
    "answer": "Yoga"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was Sean Gunn's characters name in the pilot?",
    "choices": ["Mike","Michael","Mick","Mickey"],
    "answer": "Mick"
  },
  {
    "question": "When Lorelai and Emily go the the spa, what was the name of the lipstick Emily borrows?",
    "choices": ["Vicious Trollop","Femme Fatale","Lady Of The Night","Red"],
    "answer": "Vicious Trollop"
  },
  {
    "question": "What state was Richard working in when Emily had her botched LASIK?",
    "choices": ["South Dakota","North Dakota","Philadelphia","Ohio"],
    "answer": "South Dakota"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the name of Babette's cat that they held a funeral for?",
    "choices": ["Cumin","Cinnamon","Apricot","Fluffy"],
    "answer": "Cinnamon"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was Kirk's cats name?",
    "choices": ["Luke","Captain","Trekkie","Kirk"],
    "answer": "Kirk"
  },
  {
    "question": "What did Jackson find growing in a back field on his property?",
    "choices": ["Marijuana","Cucumbers","Pickles","Poppies"],
    "answer": "Marijuana"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the name of Luke's niece?",
    "choices": ["Doula","April","Georgia","Cindy"],
    "answer": "Doula"
  },
  {
    "question": "What sandwich did Luke remove when he made new menus?",
    "choices": ["BLT","Club Sandwich","Grilled Cheese","Monte Cristo"],
    "answer": "Monte Cristo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What park in New York did Rory find Jess at?",
    "choices": ["Washington Square Park","Central Park","Brooklyn Bridge Park","Bryant Park"],
    "answer": "Washington Square Park"
  },
  {
    "question": "What were Paris's PSAT scores?",
    "choices": ["730 Verbal, 750 Math","740 Verbal, 750 Math","700 Verbal, 730 Math","680 Verbal, 700 Math"],
    "answer": "730 Verbal, 750 Math"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who did Mrs. Kim offer to let take Lane to her prom?",
    "choices": ["Young Chui","Dave","Zack","Chris"],
    "answer": "Young Chui"
  },
  {
    "question": "What dish did Lane eat at her prom?",
    "choices": ["Chicken Piccata","Spaghetti","Chicken Alfredo","Chicken Florentine"],
    "answer": "Chicken Piccata"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the flashback, what does Lorelai throw on the floor?",
    "choices": ["Sweater","Backpack","Jacket","Skirt"],
    "answer": "Sweater"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the name of Miss Patty's one woman show?",
    "choices": ["Buckle Up, I'm Patty","Hold On, It's Patty","Patty's One Woman Show","All About Patty"],
    "answer": "Buckle Up, I'm Patty"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did Christopher and Lorelai get married?",
    "choices": ["Greece","Stars Hollow","Paris","Hartford"],
    "answer": "Paris"
  },
  {
    "question": "What did Lorelai cook to get Rory to come over when she got back from France?",
    "choices": ["Nachos","Pizza","Salmon","Snails"],
    "answer": "Snails"
  },
  {
    "question": "What musical group does Lorelai qoute to Jess when he tries to pick up Rory?",
    "choices": ["Beach Boys","Beatles","Korn","The Bangles"],
    "answer": "Beach Boys"
  },
  {
    "question": "What magnet does Lindsey buy Rory in the anecdote?",
    "choices": ["Mark Twain","Abe Lincoln","Paul Bunyun","Elvis"],
    "answer": "Mark Twain"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rory goes on a date with Robert, what fake last name does she give him?", 
    "choices": ["Smith","Grimaldi","Johnson","Bronski"],
    "answer": "Grimaldi"
  },
  {
    "question": "What concert did Jess take Rory to after the hockey game?",
    "choices": ["The Pixies", "Distiller", "PJ Harvey", "Maroon 5"],
    "answer": "Distiller"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Emily's fashion consultant?",
    "choices": ["Anna", "Miss Celine", "Ms. Patty", "Lulu"],
    "answer": "Miss Celine"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the length of measurement called that was used specifically at Yale?",
    "choices": ["Spork","Yike","Kropog","Krigop"],
    "answer" : "Kropog"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the name printed on Sookie's wedding invitiations?",
    "choices": ["Suzie","Sara","Sam","Stephanie"],
    "answer": "Suzie"
  },
  {
    "question": "When Rory moved out of her grandparents house, whose home did she move into?",
    "choices": ["Lorelai's", "Lane's", "Luke's", "Babette's"],
    "answer": "Lane's"
  },
  {
    "question": "What item did Rory steal when she had her first kiss?",
    "choices": ["Corn Starch", "Mouse Trap", "Lettuce", "Pop"],
    "answer": "Corn Starch"
  },
  {
    "question": "What movie did Lorelai and Rory watch the first time Dean came over?",
    "choices": ["Willy Wonka", "Casablanca", "You've Got Mail", "Gladiator"],
    "answer": "Willy Wonka"
  },
  {
    "question": "What food item did Lorelai eat that made her think she was pregnant?",
    "choices": ["Orange", "Salad", "Apple", "Corn"],
    "answer": "Apple"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the name in Rory's first school ID at Yale?",
    "choices": ["Rory","Lorelai","Leigh","Rony"],
    "answer": "Rony"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the name of Jackson's cousin that went on a blind date with Lorelai?",
    "choices": ["Bo", "Rune","Mike","Alex"],
    "answer": "Rune"
  },
  {
    "question": "What did Emily make Rory watch videotapes of to hold her hostage",
    "choices": ["Ballroom Dancing", "Dinner Etiquette", "Family Videos", "Vacation Slide Shows"],
    "answer": "Ballroom Dancing"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Lorelai's middle name?",
    "choices": ["Victoria", "Trix", "Kim", "Lynn"],
    "answer": "Victoria"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who crashed a vehicle into Luke's diner?",
    "choices": ["Zack", "Jess", "Rory", "Kirk"],
    "answer": "Kirk"
  },
  {
    "question": "Whose vehicle was crashed into Luke's diner?",
    "choices": ["Taylor","Chris","Michel","Jackson"],
    "answer": "Taylor"
  },
  {
    "question": "What mask was the girl wearing when Rory sees her in the bathroom at Yale?",
    "choices": ["Lion", "Zebra", "Tiger", "Gorilla"],
    "answer": "Gorilla"
  },
  {
    "question": "When Michel babysits for Sookie, what does he think the baby's name is?",
    "choices": ["Davey", "Truman", "Theo", "Jack"],
    "answer": "Truman"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Lane's band?",
    "choices": ["Hep Alien", "Devils Advocate", "Follow Me To The Edge Of The Dessert", "Dave Plus Three"],
    "answer": "Hep Alien"
  },
  {
    "question": "When the Independence Inn catches fire, how does Rory entertain the kids?",
    "choices": ["Shadow Puppets","Reads a Book","Sings a Song","Sock Puppets"],
    "answer":""
  },
  {
    "question":"What does Paris watch after the CSPAN speech debacle?",
    "choices":["Gameshows","Soaps","Sesame Street","Cartoons"],
    "answer":"Soaps"
  },
  {
    "question":"Which family shows up and displaces Lorelai after the fire at the Independence Inn?",
    "choices":["The Hangitoals","The Hatlestads","The Gilmores","The Heidsmans"],
    "answer":"The Hatlestads"
  },
  {
    "question":"Where does Lorelai spend the night when she is displaced after the fire at the Independence Inn?",
    "choices":["Her Parents House","Sookie's House","Luke's Apartment","Mrs. Slutsky's Apartment"],
    "answer":"Luke's Apartment"
  },
  {
    "question":"Which is not a reason Rory thinks Young Chui is in love with Lane?",
    "choices":["Calls her every night","Asks her to tell jokes","Asks to be updated about her math test","Buys her flowers"],
    "answer":"Buys her flowers"
  },
  {
    "question":"Why was Lorelai a sore spot in Nicole and Luke's relationship?",
    "choices":["She can tell he loves her","He talks about her a lot on their first date","He's always fixing things at her house","Luke and Lorelai have inside jokes"],
    "answer":"He talks about her a lot on their first date"
  },
  {
    "question":"What gift does the Poe Society give Lorelai?",
    "choices":["Raven","Crow","Sloth","Cat"],
    "answer":"Raven"
  },
  {
    "question":"What is the dish called that Richard makes for Friday night dinner?",
    "choices":["Alex Cleaver","Josh Knives","Johnny Machete","John Butters"],
    "answer":"Johnny Machete"
  },
  {
    "question":"What was Tobin's first gift to Lorelai for her birthday?",
    "choices":["Candle","Jacket","Journal","Bagels"],
    "answer":"Candle"
  },
  {
    "question":"Which body part does Paris get pierced following Rory's 'advice'",
    "choices":["Ear","Nose","Tongue","Eyebrow"],
    "answer":"Nose"
  },
  {
    "question":"What year did Lane hit a snag when she's making a playlist for Lorelai's birthday?",
    "choices":["1978","1982","1984","1974"],
    "answer":"1974"
  }, 
    {
    "question":"According to Jess, how far is Yale from Stars Hollow?",
    "choices":["26.2 miles","28.2 miles","22.8 miles","22.6 mmiles"],
    "answer":"22.8 miles"
  },
  {
    "question":"What school does Louise go to?",
    "choices":["Yale","Princton","Brandies","Tulane"],
    "answer":"Tulane"
  },
  {
    "question":"What does Rory attempt to make the 'Worlds biggest' version of for Lorelai's birthday?",
    "choices":["Cupcake","Mallowmar","Taco","Pizza"],
    "answer":"Pizza"
  },
  {
    "question":"How much money does Richard give to Lorelai for her investment?",
    "choices":["75,000","7,500","57,000","5,700"],
    "answer":"75,000"
  },
  {
    "question":"What was Lorelai's bunny named?",
    "choices":["Fresco","Fiesta","Murray","Marshall"],
    "answer":"Murray"
  }
]






